lsnewsgroup.com 2014-02-13

# Privacy Policy | Sinclair News.Net

**Privacy Policy**

**Comments and E-mails**

As of January 16, 2012, this site is owned by LS News Group (LSNG)/Larry Sinclair LLC. I am the founder, chairman, and 100 percent owner of LS News Group/Larry Sinclair LLC. In order to register to post comments, you must provide LSNG/Larry Sinclair LLC with a valid e-mail address. LSNG/Larry Sinclair LLC will retain that e-mail address on its servers. You may also provide other information such as your name. This too will be retained on /LSNG/Larry Sinclair LLC’s server. However, LSNG/Larry Sinclair LLC won’t share any of this information with anyone except its contractors and under certain extraordinary circumstances as described below. LSNG/Larry Sinclair LLC will cancel your registration and block you from re-registering with that e-mail address if you violate its terms of use.

If you send me an e-mail, your e-mail address typically will be displayed at the top of your message. I retain most of the messages I receive, so your address likely will remain on record in my e-mail archives. These archives are stored on servers owned by a third party (currently Hostmonster, Inc)

**Ad servers**

This site uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit LSNG/Larry Sinclair LLC domains which include LSNewsGroup.com; LarrySinclair.info; LarrySinclair.org; LarrySinclair.com and LarrySinclair.net (collectively “LSNG”). These advertising companies may use information (not including your name, address, or e-mail address) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

**Cookies**

This site may use cookies to record your log file and, if you’ve registered to comment, to remember your  **LSNG** login and password. LSNG/Larry Sinclair LLC may also grant permission to advertisers to use cookies in their ads. Cookies are small text files placed automatically on your hard drive by your web browser when you visit certain websites in order to make those sites easier to use. You can configure your browser to disable cookies and/or to alert you when new ones are being sent, but please note that some features of this site might not work properly if you do so.

**Disclosure**

LSNG/Larry Sinclair LLC reserves the right to disclose information it has collected from your log file. In addition, if you’ve registered to comment, LSNG/Larry Sinclair LLC reserves the right to disclose your e-mail address and other registration information in the following three extraordinary circumstances: (a) if the chairman of LSNG/Larry Sinclair LLC believes in good faith that he/she is required to do so by law or (b) if the chairman of /LSNG/Larry Sinclair LLC believes in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to defend this site’s infrastructure or legal rights or (c) if the chairman of LSNG/Larry Sinclair LLC is asked to do so by a law enforcement agency. If you send LSNG/Larry Sinclair LLC an e-mail message, we will assume that you consent to your message—including your name, e-mail address, and IP address—being reprinted in full on our website should we deem that information worthy of publication. If you do not consent to that information being made public, please say so in your message.

**Threatening and/or abusive communications**

Notwithstanding any of the foregoing provisions, LSNG/Larry Sinclair LLC reserves the right to collect, disclose, and publicize user data, IP addresses, e-mail addresses, and any and all other personal information about anyone who, in any format or by any medium, including comments left on LSNG sites, threatens himself or others. LSNG/Larry Sinclair LLC will not honor requests for privacy attached to such threatening communications. LSNG/Larry Sinclair LLC further reserves the right to share any such data and information related to threatening communications with any local, state, and federal law enforcement agency, either voluntarily or in response to an agency’s simple request.

**Miscellaneous**

This privacy policy applies to LSNG sites identified above. It does not apply to this site’s advertisers, websites to which we link, or any other third party. For information about a third party’s privacy policy, please consult its individual website.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, LSNG/Larry Sinclair LLC reserves the right to transfer or assign the data collected from our users in the event of a merger, acquisition, sale, pending merger, pending acquisition, or pending sale. In the event of bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, LSNG/Larry Sinclair LLC may not be able to control how its user data are disposed of.

This privacy policy may be revised from time to time. Please check this page periodically for updates. Your use of this site on any given date indicates your acceptance to the terms of this policy as of that date.

/s/

Lawrence W. (Larry) Sinclair

LS News Group/Larry Sinclair LLC

_Last updated: January 17, 2012_
